Preliminary Inventory to the Stephen Denis Kertesz Papers, 1932-1986
Hoover Institution Archives
- IN WOODEN BOX
  - In large green folder, marked XV 10 Magyar Külügyminisztérium Békeelökészitö osztály. Földmüvelésügyi Minisztérium Anyaga:
    - Agrárpolitikai Tudományos Kutató Intézetek Munkaközössége. Elözetes összeállitás, kézirat gyanánt. Mekkora a mezögazdaság feltétlen szükséglete a legfontosabb gépekbol és eszközökböl, összehasonlitva a jelenlegi mennyiségekkel. Item 24. (MIMEOGRAPHED)
    - Magyar Gazdaságkutato Intézet. A jövedelem átrétegezödés hatása az ipari és egyéb nem östermelö népesség fogyasztására a föbb élelmiszerekböl. Budapest, Item 25. (MIMEOGRAPHED), 1945
    - Agrárpolitikai Tudományos Kutató Intézetek Munkaközössége. Birtokmegoszlás és agrártársadalmi rétegezödés a Birtokreform után. Item 26. (MIMEOGRAPHED)
    - Agrárpolitikai Ügyosztály. Budapest, Összehasonlitó kimutatás. Item 27. (MIMEOGRAPHED), 1945, Oktober 27
  - In large green folder marked CSEHSZLOVÁK ANYAG
    - The Slovaks and the Desintegration of the Chechoslovak Republic. (MIMEOGRAPHED, BOUND)
    - A Bodrogköz (MIMEOGRAPHED, BOUND)
    - A délszlovákiai Magyarság a Nyugati és Csehszlovák térköpen. (MIMEOGRAPHED BOUND)
    - Délszlovákiai Magyar Népesség. (MIM EOGRAPHED, BOUND)
    - The Hungarian Population of South Slovakia (MIMEOGRAPHED, BOUND)
    - The Hungarian Problem in Relation to Chechoslovákia (MIMEOGRAPHED, BOUND)
    - Garam Ipolyvölgy (MIMEOGRAPHED, BOUND)
    - Mátyusföld (MIMEOGRAPHED, BOUND)
    - Délgömöri Terület (MIMEOGRAPHED, BOUND)
    - Csallóköz (MIMEOGRAPHED, BOUND)
    - Statistics and maps in large pink envelope
      THE CONTENTS OF THESE LAST TWO LARGE FOLDERS SEEM TO BE THE ORGANIZED MATERIAL BY SUBJECT FOR THE PEACE PREPARATION. SOME OF THE ITEMS ARE TO BE FOUND LOOSE AS DUPLICATES IN THIS SAME WOODEN BOX
- Diplomacy Under the Heel of Dictators (Box 96, Bundle Bundle C, Folder 1)
- Diplomacy in the Shadow of the Red Star: The Case of Hungary (Old text - Original text) (Folder 2)
- Free/Radio/Interview - Early, 1970 (Folder 3)
- Quest for Peace - Early Chapters (Bundle Bundle C-I, Folder 1)
- Russia Grasps Hungarian Economy (Old Text) (Folder 2)
- Peace Plans (Folder 3)
- Disarmament (Folder 4)
- Bob Fitzsimmons - World History (Folder 5)
- Text on Diplomacy to Be Considered) (Box 97, Bundle Bundle C-II, Folder 1)
- International Political Institutions and Problems of the Modern World (Folder 2)
- Diplomacy - New Draft (Folder 3)
- McDougal - Yale Approach - Bibliography (Folder 4)
- League, U.N. and other Materials on Diplomacy (Box 98, Bundle Bundle C-III, Folder 1)
- Quest for Peace Through Diplomacy (Bundle Bundle C-IV, Folder 1)
- Austria and the Role of Neutral Nations in Europe (Folder 2)
- The American Task: Diplomacy for a Better Future (Folder 3)
- Chronology, Basic Data and Bibliography on East Central Europe 1955 (Folder 4)
- Peaceful Settlement of International Disputes - Development of International Arbitartion - The Hague Peace Conferences (Bundle Bundle C-V, Folder 1)
- History and Work of the Mixed Arbitral Tribunal After World War I - Private Property in International Law - Diplomatic Protection of Citizens Abroad (Box 99, Bundle Bundle C-VI, Folder 1)
- Drafts on Diplomacy and Foreign Policy (Bundle Bundle C-VII, Folder 1)
- Material on Diplomacy (Folder 2)
- Problems of U.S. Diplomacy in the 20th Century (Folder 3)
- Legal Aspects of Diplomacy - American Diplomacy in the 20th Century - Diplomacy under Dean Rusk (Folder 4)
- Problems of a Universal World Organization (Folder 5)
- United States Collective Defense Arrangements (Folder 6)
- Marxism, Communism and Western Society (Folder 7)
- Diplomacy Material to be Organized (Folder 8)
- Diplomacy of Some Important Countries (Bundle Bundle C-VIII, Folder 1)
- The Third World (Box 100, Bundle Bundle C-IX, Folder 1)
- Poor and Rich Nations (Folder 2)
- Notes and Materials Received from Robert Fluker (Folder 3)
- Spheres in China, the Boxer Rebellion and the Russo-Japanese War (Folder 4)
- The American Foreign Service and the Organization of American Foreign Service Abroad (Folder 5)
- The Professional Diplomacy in American Thinking and Practice (Box 100, Bundle Bundle C-X, Folder 1)
- The Role of Professional Diplomacy in American Thinking and Practice (Folder 2)
- Smith Simpson, et al (Folder 3)
- Foreign Services of Several Countries (Bundle Bundle C-XI, Folder 1)
- New Dimensions of Foreign Policy - Television (Folder 2)
- Articles and Papers on Diplomacy (Folder 3)
- Various Drafts - General texts on diplomacy and Diplomatic Negotiations (Folder 4)
- Conference on Professional Diplomacy (Folder 5)
- Addresses - European and East-West Problems in the 1970's (Folder 6)
- Articles on Diplomacy (Folder 7)
- Role of Ideology - Soviet-U.S. Diplomacy (Folder 8)
- Diplomacy - Tocqueville and Baron Burian's Letter (Folder 9)
- U.S. Domestic Political Considerations (Box 101, Bundle Bundle C-XII, Folder 1)
- Drafts on American Foreign Policy and Diplomacy (Bundle Bundle C-XIII, Folder 1)
- U.S. Foreign Policy and Diplomacy (Bundle Bundle C-XIV, Folder 1)
- Preparations for Peace in the U.S.A (Folder 2)
- American Foreign Policy - Objectives and Priorities of American Foreign Policy (Folder 3)
- National Priorities (Folder 4)
- Interaction of United States and Western Europe (Folder 5)
- U. S. and Communist Responses to a Changing World (Folder 6)
- Science and Technology (Folder 7)
- Spiritual Values and Soviet Diplomacy (Folder 8)
- Kissinger's Proposal for a New Relation Between U.S.A. and Europe, (1973) (Folder 9)
- Diplomacy in World Politics (Folder 10)
- U.S.A. In the 1950s (Bundle Bundle C-XV, Folder 1)
- Thinking about the U.S. in the 1960s (Box 102, Bundle Bundle C-XVI, Folder 1)
- About America in 1971 (Bundle Bundle C-XVII, Folder 1)
- Freedom of Press and Related Matters (Bundle Bundle C-XVIII, Folder 1)
- Articles and Writings on American Foreign Policy (Bundle Bundle C-XIX, Folder 1)
- Articles -, 1970-1972 (Folder 2)
- The Cold War: Material on United States and Soviet Policy in Eastern Europe (Bundle Bundle C-XX, Folder 1)
- Cold War and Hungary (Folder 2)
- Detente and Cold War in the Mid-, 1970s (Box 103, Bundle Bundle C-XXI, Folder 1)
- Mixed Correspondence - Committee on International Relations (Folder 2)
- Bibliography (Folder 3)
- Law of the Sea (Bundle Bundle C-XXII, Folder 1)
- International Law - Bibliography (Folder 2)
- American Contribution to International Law (Folder 3)
- International Law - - Discussed Questions, Fall 1974 (Folder 4)
- Booklet - Confronting Moscow (Folder 5)
- U.S.-Soviet Material (Folder 6)
- Soviet Foreign Policy and Diplomacy (Mainly Notes) (Folder 7)
- Soviet Power - How to Deal with the Russians (Folder 8)
- Technique of Communist Conquest - Old and Largely Unused Material (Folder 9)
- American Diplomacy and Diplomats '49 (Box 104, Bundle Bundle C-XXIII, Folder 1)
- American Diplomacy and American Diplomats (Folder 2)
- Diplomats (Symposium) (Folder 3)
- Relevant Passages from Murphy's Memoirs (Folder 4)
- Strategic Policy and American Government: Structural Constants and Variables (Folder 5)
- Kissinger-Nixon Diplomacy 1972-k863-1974 (Bundle Bundle C-XXIV, Folder 1)
- Vorleistung - Meaning of Detente for U.S. Foreign Policy and Related U.S. Problems in World Affairs Revisionism - Trade Policy and Detente, 1973-1974 (Bundle Bundle C-XXV, Folder 1)
- America's Profile in the World (Box 105, Bundle Bundle C-XXVI, Folder 1)
- As Others See Us (Folder 2)
- Comments on American Aspirations and the World Community (Folder 3)
- The United States in the Sixties (Folder 4)
- What America Stands For (Folder 5)
- Kissinger Interviewed by Reston (Folder 6)
- The Tale of American Diplomacy (Bundle Bundle C-XXVII, Folder 1)
- Murphy and American Diplomacy Texts - From Wartime Cooperation to NATO (Folder 2)
- Diplomacy and the Future As Seen in the 1960s (Folder 3)
- Robert D. Murphy and George Kennan - Mainly Bookviews (Folder 4)
- Bookviews on Russia and World War II (Folder 5)
- Booklets - Such as Democracy and Foreign Policy, The Role of Negotiations, The Unseen Search for Peace, International Security, and Strengthening the Forces of Freedom (Folder 6)
- Pamphlet - The Soviet Approach to Negotiation (Box 106, Bundle Bundle C-XXVIII, Folder 1)
- Notes (Folder 2)
- Current Digest of the Soviet Press (Folder 3)
- Methods of Soviet Foreign Policy Since WWII (Folder 4)
- Material on Soviet Diplomacy (Folder 5)
- Memorandum - Subject: The Communist Economic Offensive Through 1964 (Folder 6)
- Material to be used in "The Permanent and Changing Features of Soviet Foreign Policy (Folder 7)
- Documents and State Papers - United States Department of State (Folder 8)
- Soviet Diplomacy, Material (Folder 9)
- Soviet-American Negotiations (Folder 10)
- General Material -, July-December 1979 (Box 107, Bundle Bundle C-XXIX, Folder 1)
- - Immigration Problems, Refugees, Citizenship, 1980 (Folder 2)
- American Political Process (Folder 3)
- - Education - International Studies, 1977 (Box 108, Bundle Bundle C-XXX, Folder 1)
- The 1970s and Challenges of the 1980s - Return to Patriotism (Folder 2)
- International Competition -, 1980 (Folder 3)
- Economic and Financial Policy -, 1980 (Folder 4)
- U. S. and the Sea (Folder 5)
- Technology and Productivity in the U.S (Folder 6)
- Military and National Service (Folder 7)
- Moral Fiber of the Nation and Presidential Leadership (Folder 8)
- International Officials - Role of Personalities in International Relations (Box 109, Bundle Bundle C-XXXI, Folder 1)
- Inflation - Energy Saving, 1979 (Folder 2)
- Text on Economics (Folder 3)
- Dollar Crisis and Monetary Reform, 1971-1974 (Folder 4)
- Material concerning Quest for Peace Through Diplomacy - Correspondence, Bookreviews (Box 109-110, Bundle Bundle C-XXXII, Folder 1)
- Additional material to Quest for Peace Through Diplomacy (Folder 2)
- NATO Material - Mixed Collection (Box 110-111, Bundle Bundle C-XXXIII, Folder 1)
- Interesting Mixed Material relevant to diplomacy (Folder 2)
- Search for Peace Through Diplomacy - Lecture Material, 1975 (Folder 3)
- Problems of Contemporary U.S. Foreign Policy (Box 111, Bundle Bundle C-XXXIV, Folder 1)
- Collection of Drafts (Folder 2)
- Drafts on American Foreign Policy and Diplomacy and Articles (Folder 3)
- International Politics, etc (Folder 4)
- Disarmament (Folder 5)
- Pamphlet - Újeuropa (Folder 6)
- Notes - early drafts and sources concerning Notre Dame Magazine Article - Congressional Power in Foreign Affairs (Folder 7)
- American Diplomacy (Box 112, Bundle Bundle C-XXXIV, Folder 1)
- Papers on Diplomacy (Folder 2)
- Gaullist Foreign Policy (Folder 3)
- What Course For American Foreign Policy: View from Abroad (Folder 4)
- National Security in Historical Perspective -, 1976 (Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous (Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Diplomatic Notes (Folder 7)
- International Organization - - Claude's Book, 1960 (Folder 8)
- Notes - Source Material (Folder 9)
- European Trip and Article Material to be Dictated (Folder 10)
- The Secretary of State and the Problem of Coordination - Pamphlet of Committee on Government Operations (Bundle Bundle C-XXXV, Folder 1)
- Pamphlet - Myths and Realities: U.S. Nuclear Strategy (Folder 2)
- East Central Europe (Folder 3)
- Conference on European Problems and Studiengesellschaft Material (Bundle Bundle C-XXXVI, Folder 1)
- Material to be considered in writings (Folder 2)
- Footnotes - Between Russia and the West - Page Proofs (Box 113, Bundle Bundle C-XXXVII, Folder 1)
- Manuscript of The Last European Peace Conference (Bundle Bundle C-XXXVIII, Folder 1)
- Senator Armstrong - Republican Policy Committee Material (Bundle Bundle C-XXXIX, Folder 1)
- Memoranda addressed to William L. Armstrong (Folder 2)
- Letters to Senator Armstrong (Folder 3)
- China Diary and Pertinent Articles (Box 114, Bundle Bundle C-XXXX, Folder 1)
- NATO General Material -, 1950s (Bundle Bundle C-XXXXI, Folder 1)
- Atlantic Cooperation and Europe (Folder 2)
- Tensions Across the Atlantic (Folder 3)
- The Process of Making American Foreign Policy (Bundle Bundle C-XXXXII, Folder 1)
- The Process of Making American Foreign Policy - New Edition (Folder 2)
- Making U.S. Foreign Policy - Corscadden's Letter and Bob Fluker's Comments (Folder 3)
- Protocol - The American Council of Learned Societies and The Hungarian Academy of Sciences (Bundle Bundle C-XXXXIII, Folder 1)
- Statéments on the book Between Russia and the West (Bundle Bundle C-XXXXIV, Folder 1)
- Transylvania - Concerning Transylvania and Rumania (Bundle Bundle C-XXXXV, Folder 1)
- Notes published in the book on Transylvania - The English Translations of Auer's and Tatarescu's address at the Paris Conference (Folder 2)
- Transylvania - Material received at Kent State University (Folder 3)
- Old Text - Quest for Peace Through Diplomacy -, July 1960 (Box 115, Bundle Bundle C-XXXXVI, Folder 1)
- Questions discussed in Memoirs (Bundle Bundle C-XXXXVII, Folder 1)
- Quest For Peace Through Diplomacy - Incomplete Sets (Box 116, Bundle Bundle C-XXXXVIII, Folder 1)
- Problems of American Diplomacy - Various texts (Bundle Bundle C-XXXXIX, Folder 1)
- The Task of American Diplomacy: Policy Objectives and Methods (Box 117, Bundle Bundle C-L, Folder 1)
- Collection of Material on Diplomacy (Box 117-118, Bundle Bundle C-LI, Folder 1)
- Hungarian Material System of Government and Foreign Policy of Hungary - Source Material, 1962-1970 (Box 119, Bundle Bundle C-LII, Folder 1)
- Articles Dealing with the Hungarian Revolt (Box 119-120, Bundle Bundle C-LIII, Folder 1)
- Book - A Magyar Forradalom Es Szabadsagharc (Box 120, Bundle Bundle C-LIV, Folder 1)
- Chronology of East Central Europe Since 1939 (Box 121, Bundle Bundle C-LV, Folder 1)
- Hungary, 1955-1962 (Box 121-122, Bundle Bundle C-LVI, Folder 1)
- East Central Europe - Preface and Introduction (Box 122, Bundle Bundle C-LVII, Folder 1)
- East Central Europe - General Material (Folder 2)
- East Central Europe (Box 123, Bundle Bundle C-LVIII, Folder 1)
- East Central Europe - General material to be used in the Introduction (Folder 2)
- Communist Orbit - Secondary Material (Folder 3)
- East Central Europe (Box 124, Bundle Bundle C-LIX, Folder 1)
- East Central Europe in World Politics (Folder 2)
- East Central Europe in Recent Diplomatic Developments Summit Meetings and the Fate of East Central Europe (Folder 3)
- Rumania, Bulgaria, Czechoslovakia (Box 117, Bundle Bundle C-L, Folder 1)
- Yugoslavia, Albania (Folder 2)
- General Unorganized Material on Eastern Europe (Folder 3)
- Germany and East Europe (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous - Soviet Affairs, Fourth World Congress (Box 117-118, Bundle Bundle C-LI, Folder 1)
- Land and Peoples in History (Box 119, Bundle Bundle C-LII, Folder B.1)
- American-Soviet Diplomacy (Bundle Bundle C-LIII, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous (Box 120, Bundle Bundle C-LIV, Folder 1)
- War Prisoner (Box 121, Bundle Bundle C-LV, Folder 1)
- Communist Constitutions (Box 121-122, Bundle Bundle C-LVI, Folder 1)
- Teleki's Data on Hungary - Mining, raw material, etc (Box 122, Bundle Bundle C-LVII, Folder 1)
- Hungary - Miscellaneous (Box 122-123, Bundle Bundle C-LVIII, Folder 1)
- Mamatey - Legalizing the Collapse of Austria-Hungary at the Paris Peace Conference (Box 124, Bundle Bundle C-LVIV, Folder 1)
- Eastern Europe - Notes and Drafts (Box 125, Bundle Bundle C-LVV, Folder 1)
- General East European Material, 1963-64 (Folder 2)
- Preliminary Notes and Research Materials on Hungary (Folder 3)
- Hungary and Eastern Europe -, 1961 (Folder 4)
- Hungary -, 1963-1964 (Folder 5)
- Developments in Hungary, 1957 (Folder 6)
- Hungary - Literature, Theater and Drama (Folder 7)
- The Holy See (Folder 8)
- Hungarian Revolution - General Articles (Box 126, Bundle Bundle C-LVVI, Folder 1)
- Hungary, 1960-1961 (Folder 2)
- Hungary, 1959-1960 (Folder 3)
- Hungary, 1958-1959 (Folder 4)
- Chronology - Army and Occupation - U.N. Material (Folder 5)
- Statements by Anna Kethly and Bela Kiraly (Folder 6)
- The Hungarian New Course and Thaw - William E. Griffth, 1953-1956 (Folder 7)
- Hungary: A Survey -, July 1958 - July 1959 (Folder 8)
- The Parties and Foreign Policy - Bi-Partisanship (Bundle Bundle C-LVVII, Folder 1)
- U.N. Material (Letters), 1956 (Folder 2)
- Development of World Community and International Law - Antiquity and the Middle Ages (Bundle Bundle C-LVVIII, Folder 1)
- The Grolier Society, Inc (Bundle Bundle C-LVIX, Folder 1)
- U.N. Diplomacy, 1959 (Box 127, Bundle Bundle C-LVX, Folder 1)
- Impact of the Second World War - Parliamentary Diplomacy in the U.N. and Other International Agencies. Global Implications of Diplomacy (Folder 2)
- Diplomacy and Propaganda (Folder 3)
- American and Russian Negotiations - Negotiating Behavior (Folder 4)
- Veto and Block Voting and Neutralism (Folder 5)
- U.S. and U.N. Diplomacy (Folder 6)
- United Nations - League of Nations - American Diplomacy in the United Nations - General Problems of International Organizations - Bloc voting - World Public Opinion (Folder 7)
- The Relevance of Diplomatic History to the Practice of International Relations - (Comments on Professor Ernest R. May's paper by Stephen D. Kertesz), September 9, 1965 (Box 127, Bundle Bundle C-LVXI, Folder 1)
- International Studies Association Conference in, 1973 (March 14-17) (Folder 2)
- National Priorities (Folder 3)
- "In Search of a Hungarian-Canadian Lobby, " by N. F. Dreisziger - "Free Hungarians and the Future of Slovakia" by N. F. Dreisziger, 1927-1951 (Folder 4)
- General Texts on Eastern Europe and Hungary Papers prepared for the Seminar on, April 26, 1979 (Bundle Bundle C-LVXII, Folder 1)
- Philip E. Mosely (Box 128, Bundle Bundle C-LVXIII, Folder 1)
- Institute Reports - A Directory of International Programs and Faculty - The Interdependent World and the University of Notre Dame, (1971-1976) (1972) (Bundle Bundle C-LVXIV, Folder 1)
- Guggenheim, (1958-1959) (Box 128-129, Bundle Bundle C-LVXV, Folder 1)
- Mindzenty Text and related articles (Box 130, Bundle Bundle C-LVXVI, Folder 1)
- Man's Fate in Three Worlds (Bundle Bundle C-LVXVII, Folder 1)
- Material on Pope John Paul and the Polish Church - Catholic Church in General (Box 131, Bundle Bundle C-LVXVIII, Folder 1)
- United Nations Material - Miscellaneous (Box 128, Bundle Bundle C-LVXIV, Folder 1)
- Vatican (Box 128-129, Bundle Bundle C-LVXV, Folder 1)
- General Texts on Diplomacy (Box 130, Bundle Bundle C-LVXVI, Folder 1)
- New tasks for Diplomacy - Changing Diplomatic Theories and Practices. Diplomacy by Conference. Secret and Open Diplomacy (Folder 2)
- Old Table of Contents and Synopses (Folder 3)
- Diplomatic Requirements of the United Nations (Folder 4)
- Basic Transformations in the 20th Century (Bundle Bundle C-LVXVII, Folder 1)
- Outlook Toward the Future (Box 131, Bundle Bundle C-LVXVIII, Folder 1)
- Impact of the First World War (Bundle Bundle C-LVXIX, Folder 1)
- Development of Diplomacy (Box 129, Bundle Bundle C-LXX, Folder 1)
- Triumph and Decline of Traditional Diplomach, 1815-1914 (Folder 2)
- American Diplomacy (Folder 3)
- Material on American Diplomacy, 1958-59 (Folder 4)
- Challenges and Responses of American Diplomacy (Folder 5)
- American Foreign Policy and World Problems, (1955-1957) (Box 130, Bundle Bundle C-LXXI, Folder 1)
- Notes on American Foreign Policy and Diplomacy, (1958-1959) (Folder 2)
- Introduction Material to American Diplomacy Since World War II - Making American Foreign Policy and United States and NATO (Folder 3)
- Diplomacy and Foreign Policy (Folder 4)
- Transnational political parties - Socialism - Labor Unions (Bundle Bundle C-LXXII, Folder 1)
- Truman's Speech, (9-7-56) (Box 131, Bundle Bundle C-LXXIII, Folder 1)
- Addendum (Box 132-133)
  - Bibliographies (Bundle Bundle A)
  - Bozeman - Politics & Culture in Int'l Politics (Bundle Bundle B, Folder 1)
- Decision Making as an Approach to the Study of Int'l Politics (Folder 2)
- An Appropriate Role for the Military in American Foreign Policy Making (Folder 3)
- Hungary Used Sources, 1921-82 (Bundle Bundle C)
- Additional Itemized Materials (Box 132-133)
  - Statisztikai Adatok (Bundle BUNDLE _____)
  - Magyar belpolitikai, kulpolitikai és gazdasági adatok
  - Adatok nagy újjáépitésre
  - Hungary - Ad. VI (Mixed Material)
  - The art of Cooperation - US USSR Relations (Bundle BUNDLE _____)
  - Unorganized typed notes
  - Eastern Europe & the USSR (Interplay 1967 - 1969)
  - Dittoes & Stencils
  - Notes on European Trip in 1970 (Bundle BUNDLE _____)
  - US & Europe
  - Material to be considered for Trans-Atlantic Relations
  - Europe & USA
  - Typed texts; Europe to US
  - US - _____ Relations
  - Outlines; New Horizons in World Affairs
  - Trans-Atlantic Relations
  - A text for the American chapter __________
  - Problems of American Foreign Policy & Diplomacy
- INCREMENT, JULY 1986
  - Correspondence (Box 134-155)
  - Subject file (Box 155-179)
- Microfilm reel: Hungarian newspapers, Kis Ujság, August 1946-October, 1951 (Microfilm reel 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  Contains: Kis Ujság, August 1946-October 1947 and Szabad Nép, July 1946-November 1946. Filmed by the Library of Congress, 1951.